[{"answer": "Everything's so tiny, tiny.  Tiny. Everything.  Won't you please come over? Help.  I need somebody.  Won't you please please help me", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Her mother?  Her mother said", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "She's overheated and not eating enough. How often are you feeding her", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What's a lot", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What are you doing here now?!  Her first sound sleep, not a sound, not a sound", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh my god, Video Night.  First Thursday of the month.  Video night at my friend's house.  I'm sorry, I forgot", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "If you and Mommy liked each other enough to have me, how come you're not together anymore", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "When you fall out of love where do you land", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Daddy, did God mean for you to be like this or was it an accident", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I mean you're different", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Do you mean", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What do you mean?  I mean, what do you mean", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, I've always been smart", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I can be a mother.  A real good mother", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You're lucky.  I'm looking for a smart, good mother", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh, good.  Good", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Okay okay.  I can be very gentle", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I got stories up the wazoo.  Why don't you come with me.  I'll tell you a nice story", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes.  Now read the word", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No you're not", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, you don't want to say that.  you don't want them to know you're not home", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Everybody's lying", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "My treat.  My treat", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I said it's my treat.  That means I'll get it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Don't be ridiculous.  I'll get it", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend, do you really want to get it or are you just trying to", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Trying to what", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Like a what", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You know, trying to act like a", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Like a...a..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Do you think what they think?  my friend can't order food.  my friend can't pay a check.  my friend can't take care of my friend", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're my lawyer it matters what you think", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter what I think", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Hey, it doesn't matter to them what I think", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I wish I had a mother like that.  She must have been smart", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Do you have any idea what her IQ was", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I heard you turned seven this year. That's pretty exciting", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What'd you get for your birthday", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sorry.  I was confused.  I thought you didn't open your birthday presents because you ran away from your own party when your best friend told everyone that you were adopted", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Why would your friends say it if you hadn't said it", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I answer in one sentence", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes.  One sentence.  Short and sweet. My aunt was short and sweet.  But her cooking was too spicy she..", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Excuse me.  Now Ms. my friend, in all the time you've known them, have you ever questioned my friend's ability as a father", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Never", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well who did he say was taking care of you", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I am working late", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Can't you grasp the concept of manipulating the truth?  Not lying. Just a little tweak here and there", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "He doesn't want to play with me", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "No...You're so lucky.  You get to play with my friend all the time", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Yes he does.  He does he does.  He thinks you don't want to", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "But who are you kidding?  Isn't my friend already smarter than you", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You think", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "In some ways.  But in other ways, she's not, I think", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I think", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " my friend needs me", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "my friend needs you", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well then where were you living", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "So your parents put you in an institution", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Some yes.  Some on.  Some yes", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Sometimes.  Sometimes they did sometimes", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "you have the mental capacity of a seven year old.  So you ask yourself, a seven year old", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "How to parent a fellow seve", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "my friend doesn't need me anymore.  She has a new family.  She doesn't need me anymore", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "She didn't have to say it.  I may be stupid, but I know.  I know", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Try harder", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Is that right?  Everyone else is perfect but only my friend feels loss and pain", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "People like me", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "There's one option we've never talked about, my friend.  I know what you went through the last time you took the stand.  We could settle out of court, ask for the most incredible visitation rights", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I'm not saying you don't have a chance", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I know, but if you", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I didn't say that.  But do you want to go", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Nevermind", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Fine", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "I live here.  This is where I live", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I wanted to be close to you.  I wanted to be closer.  Look at my apartment number.  my friend was born on October 9th.  His son was born on October 9th", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "my friend met my friend on November 9th", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "that place.  9 letters.  that place", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Nobody believed that my friend could really be a song writer.  But he wrote", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "my friend's was my friend", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "I-am-Sam.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Promise..", "qsentId": 82}]